

610 Purdue Mall, West Lafayette, IN, 47907

□ (415)203-8543 | ☑ chi45@purdue.edu | ♠ hyung-gun.me | □ stnoah1 | □ hyung-gun | ➢ Hyung-gun Chi

Research Interests

My research interests lie at the intersection of Computer Vision and Robotics, focusing on 3D Geometric Deep Learning for recognizing and synthesizing 3D objects. In this area, I applied machine learning (deep learning) algorithms for Augmented/Virtual Reality and Smart Factory.

Education

Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

MASTER OF SCIENCE IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

• Advisor: Karthik Ramani, Donald W.Feddersen Professor of Mechanical Engineering

Yonsei University Seoul, South Korea

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

- · Advisor: Soo-Hong Lee, Professor of Mechanical Engineering
- 2011-2013, 2-year military service

Skills

Programming Python, Matlab, C/C++, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP

Frameworks TensorFlow, PyTorch, Keras, ROS, OpenCV

Software Creo Parametric, SolidWorks, HyperWorks, GAZEBO

Publications and Patents_

Journal Papers

- [J4][PDF] S. Kim, H. G. Chi and Karthik Ramani. "Object synthesis by learning part geometry with surface and volumetric representations" (2019) Computer-Aided Design, submitted.
- [J3][PDF] S. Kim, N. Winovich, H. G. Chi, G. Lin, and K. Ramani (2019). Latent transformations neural network for object view synthesis. The Visual Computer, pp. 1-15.
- [J2][PDF] H. T. Hwang, H. G. Chi, N. K. Kang, H. B. Kong and Soo-Hong Lee. "An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification" (2019) Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST), 33(3), pp. 1333-1339.
- [J1][PDF] JIN YONGZHU, H. G. Chi and Soo-Hong Lee. "A Study on the Optimal Design of Pedestrian Robots Using Jansen Mechanism". (2016) Korean Journal of Computational Design and Engineering, 22(2), pp. 18-22.

Conference Proceedings

- [C3][PDF] L. Paredes, X. Qian, H. G. Chi and Karthik Ramani. "ControllAR: Design and Fabrication of a Universal Parametric Low-Profile Hand Wearable for Augmented Reality Interactions" (2019) Proceedings of the SIGCHI conference on human factors in computing systems, submitted.
- [C2][PDF] H. Hwang, H. G. Chi, S. H. Lee. "A Research about 3D Design Data Classification with 3D Convolutional Neural Network" (2017) Proceedings of the Society for Computational Design and Engineering Conference, pp. 441-442.
- [C1][PDF] M. H. Woo, S. H. Kim, H. G. Chi, M. W. Park, J. K. Kim and S. H. Lee. "Development of Web-based, Module Structure Platform for Surgical Workflow Management". (2016) Proceedings of the Society for Computational Design and Engineering Conference, pp. 439-441.

Patents

• [P1][PDF] H. G. Chi. "Computer Input Automation System" KR Patent (2017): 10-1745330.

Research Experience

Hand motion prediction with RGBD-T data

C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Jul. 2019 - Present

Aug. 2018 - PRESENT

Mar 2010 - Feb 2017

- Proposed a novel dataset by fusing RGB-D and thermal data for action recognition.
- · Developed a method which predicts hand motion by segmenting hands and objects with a 3D Deep Neural network dealing with RGBD-T data.

A Large-scale Engineering Part Benchmark Dataset

C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Feb. 2019 - Present

- Collected massive mechanical component CAD data with a web-scrapper, and expanded the data for dense data distribution using Creo Parametric and SolidWorks API.
- Developed a web-based 3D CAD search engine using a 3D Deep Neural Network and PostgreSQL database.
- · Benchmarked state-of-art 3D Deep Neural Network for classification and segmentation task to evaluate the dataset.

Part Geometry Net (PGNet)

C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT Oct. 2018 - Aug. 2019

• Built a Generative Adversarial Network which generates 3D objects given a discrete category condition and continuous instance-level attributes by fusing the various types of geometric information.

• Introduced a part identifier module which learns part geometry to preserve part properties of 3D objects. (Relevant publication: [J4])

Latent Transformation Neural Network (LTNN)

C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - April. 2019

· Developed a fully-convolutional conditional generative network which is capable of view synthesis using a light-weight neural network suited for real-time applications. Introduced the conditional transformation unit which is designed to learn the latent space transformations corresponding to specified target views. (Relevant publication: [J3])

Visual Programming Language for Mobile Robots and IoT Nodes

C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - Feb. 2019

- · Proposed a web-based visual and spatial programming language that allows novice users and small industries to program mobile robots and IoT Nodes to execute planned tasks.
- Developed a virtual world using Robotic Operating System(ROS) and GAZEBO which simulates interaction between mobile robots and IoT devices.

ControllAR C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - Dec. 2018

· Proposed a parametrizing interface, simple and accessible fabrication workflow, and a pressure sensor using a soft piezoresistive elastomer material. Also, developed embedded system using Arduino and analyzed signals from different sensors and materials. (Relevant publication: [C3])

3D Deep Neural Network evaluation method

Knowledge-Based Design LAB, Yonsie Univ.

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Feb. 2016 - Jul. 2017

· Proposed an evaluation method for 3D Deep Neural Networks by visualizing the impact of each voxel of each 3D objects and also a web-based 3D CAD search engine using a 3D Deep Neural Network for demonstration. (Relevant publication: [J2][C2])

Web-based Surgical Workflow Management Platform

Knowledge-Based Design LAB, Yonsie Univ.

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Feb. 2016 - Aug. 2016

· Developed a web-based interface and database for integrated surgical information, to optimize surgical procedures and reduce the medical loss caused by communication errors and lack of information. (Relevant publication: [C1])

Working Experience

Python Developer

Seoul, South Korea

FINANCIAL INSIGHT

Jan. 2018 - Jul. 2018

• Worked as a Python developer in an early-stage startup company. Developed a web-scrapper and database for collecting financial data of the Korean stock market.

Python Developer and CEO

Seoul, South Korea

NEIL LAB CORPORATION

Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2017 • Developed an office automation system using Python specifically for automating tasks such as sending an e-mail or issuing receipts,

- and designed a back-end system and database for customer web-service which automatically scrap and integrate customer's financial and personal data. (Relevant patent: [P1])
- Founded and led a startup company as a CEO for a year and also worked as a Python developer. The company was funded \$ 30,000 by the Seongnam Industry Promotion Agency.

Mechanic and Squad leader

Inje, South Korea

REPUBLIC OF KOREA ARMY

Apr. 2011 – Jan. 2013

- Maintained military weapons and equipment including firearms and vehicles.
- Led a squad as a squad leader; honored as a distinguished soldier.

Extracurricular Activity

Habitat for Humanity Korea Campus Chapter

South Korea

MEMBER & PRESIDENT

Mar. 2010 - Aug. 2016

- Constructed new houses for the homeless and renovated old houses, served more than 500 hours.
- Led and managed a volunteer group for a year; received the first honor from 2014 Yonsei Club Evaluation.

Korea Food for the Hungry International - campus volunteer group

South Korea

Apr. 2013 - Nov. 2013

Mentored preschool children and elementary school students at the Seoul Children's Center

Honors & Awards

2016 KISTI (Korea Institute of Science and Technology Information) President's Award,
Edison Challenge – Computer Aided Design Section

CDE (Korea Society for Computational Design and Engineering) President's Award,
CDE Challenge – Computational Design and Engineering Tools Section

Daejeon, South Korea